movieflix.com 2000-06-10

# Privacy Statement

**TRUSTe Licensee**

Code 7 Entertainment, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the MovieFlix.com Web site. When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of: What personally identifiable information of yours is collected; What organization is collecting the information; How the information is used; With whom the information may be shared; What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control; and How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Robert Moskovits by E-mail at: [info@MovieFlix.com](mailto:info@movieflix.com). If the Web site has not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/watchdog.html). 

Code 7 Entertainment, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [www.MovieFlix.com](http://www.movieflix.com/). 

**Information Collected**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Certain buttons within our Web site serve cookies each time you enter without actually clicking the button. MovieFlix.com does not receive any information about you from these cookies. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like names and email addresses) and demographic information (like their zip code, and gender). If you require additional information about MovieFlix.com please refer to [http://www.movieflix.com/contact.htm](http://www.movieflix.com/contact.htm). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. MovieFlix.com does not share any user information with third parties. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

This site contains links to other sites; www.MovieFlix.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes use of message boards to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor by un-checking the "request Movieflix news" notify box. MovieFlix.com gives users the opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe from MovieFlix news. Our site lets users unsubscribe to MovieFlix news by sending us email at [info@MovieFlix.com](mailto:info@movieflix.com). 

**Change/Modify**

MovieFlix.com currently does not have a method in place where users can update and change their information. We welcome any comments or suggestions regarding this matter. MovieFlix.com will obtain written or active email consent from the user if the site will be using the information collected from the user in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection. 

**Off-Site Security Measures**

MovieFlix.com's privacy policy is reviewed on a monthly basis with all employees. Access to data is obtained via secure passwords. Access to data is only limited to two (2) people responsible for privacy. 

**MovieFlix Store**

MovieFlix.com has an e-commerce relationship with Moletown. When a user goes to Moletown, they are giving their personal information to that site. Moletown uses their own cookies and MovieFlix does not have access to these cookies. Moletown only shares numbers of sales per month with MovieFlix. MovieFlix.com advises users to read Moletown's privacy statement and/or security measures. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Robert Moskovits Code 7 Entertainment, Inc. P.O. Box 480764 Los Angeles, CA 90048 [info@MovieFlix.com](mailto:info@movieflix.com)
